{
    "id": "9439f55c19f648dfbbd3036321d6774d",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ask a polite question .................................. I expect a polite reply.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0500a85785af4a598c8e1a11cc3cfabf"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ill .......................................... he went to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "because",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "73fc5449eb2641d0a2ae8ae73513e11d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You may not succeed .................................... I advise you to make another attempt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "though",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a8c65677e004752ad6935a200a797ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should understand, ............................................ I explained everything in detail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "that",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "19d34d300d37488f936c968471c044c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was no point in arguing ...................................... he gave up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hence",
                "and",
                "and hence"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "989380183ffe4c4ab2a1e39c763e9b49"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was not there, .................................. we went without him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "248503974d5849a387c003bf17159cc3"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are hiding something in your left hand ..................................... I know it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "that",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "358ba6aded674b778c7abed6fc141a85"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must be in better health and ........................................ I will come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "then",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2159614640ad4c1bb32b7067bd94c4a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t see the snake .......................................... I didn’t kill it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "therefore",
                "and therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bfbe2ed0111e4fe3b9d6e75ecc35bd1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Finish your work and ............................................ you may go.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd85662f4a1f4a0b9cd37094199ec1dc"
        }
    ]
}